The Invisible Challenger
Pass it here!
Not bad.
Go, Jun!
You can do it!
Goal!
Haha! How d'ya like that?
Jun!
What the...?
Augh!
Jun, are you alright?
Ugh... what just happened?
Okay, bye!
Anna! See you tomorrow!
Jun?
You should watch where you're going.
W-What was that?
What just happened?
I don't understand what's going on today...
Augh!
What is up with me today?!
Haha! It looks like you're having a bad luck day.
No, it's not just some bad luck.
I'm sure someone must have put a curse on me!
And who would do that?
I wish I knew so I could get my hands on them!
What are you guys going on about?
Haha!
What's all over your face?!
What's wrong with your face?
You're one to talk! Have you looked in a mirror?
I would say it's an improvement.
What did you say?!
It was you, wasn't it?!
Alright, settle down!
What are you all up to?
We all got pranked real bad.
Who could have pulled such a prank?
I don't know...
I was just sunbathing in the area while you were at school.
We can get rusty if we just stay in our Metal Card forms.
When I woke up, this had happened.
Did kids in the neighborhood scribble on them?
It does seem like a childish prank.
Who are you calling childish?!
Who's there?!
What was that?!
Is it invisible?
What? What's going on?
Haha!
Show yourself!
You must be a Metal Cardbot like us!
Heh! So you figured out, huh?
Stealth mode, off!
Is it a helicopter?
No, it's a VTOL aircraft. Vertical Take-Off and Landing.
They were camouflaged to blend into their surroundings!
I think there was something else like that on Earth. Looks kinda like a lizard...
Chameleon.
Yeah, that's it.
Hey, chameleon helicopter!
Who are you?
You can call me Shadow X.
You drew on their faces, didn't you?!
Yeah, and that's not all!
I was also the one pranking you all day long!
So that was all you!
Why are you pulling pranks on everyone?
Isn't it obvious?
I. Just.
Don't.
Like.
You!
But what do you mean?
What have I ever done to you?
What did you do, Jun?
Try to remember what it was.
I didn't do anything! Hrgh...
That's it! The Metal Breath!
You're using that to seal and summon all of us Metal Cardbots,
like you're the boss around here or something!
I did no such thing!
The Metal Breath is the sign of the chosen one,
the one who will lead us.
We need it and Jun to coexist peacefully on planet Earth.
Hmph!
I refuse to submit to some goofy kid.
I want to fly high in the sky and be free!
Hey, don't call me a goofy kid, you chameleon helicopter!
I said my name is Shadow X!
Yeah?! Well, that's a stupid name for a plane!
What did you say, you little runt?!
It's an acorn measuring contest.
They must both be five years old.
You want to have it your way?
Then just try and seal me!
Only then will I be your underling!
Like those other chumps you got there!
Ugh, here we go again. Another troublesome robot appears.
Blue Cop! Let's go after him!
Roger!
How do you plan to catch a plane that can fly and become invisible?!
Hey, guys!
I'll show that helicopter what we're made of!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Stop, stop, you guys!
Where's your energy?! I need you committed on this!
Sorry, Vera...
My dance videos haven't been getting views at all lately!
Can't you put some passion into it?!
Yeah, sure...
It's the police!
We aren't allowed to be here! Let's get out of here before we get in trouble!
Hang on. Something doesn't seem right.
Hey! Vera!
He's going up towards the cranes!
First, we'll need to get Shadow X to come down!
Ha! Took you long enough to get here!
You're so slow! I was getting bored!
This guy...
Blue Cop! Prepare for battle!
Alright.
Metal Cardbot, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
I really hate how you act like such a show-off, ordering everyone around like that.
Like, you call the shots around here!
What did I do to make you so upset?
Enough talk, you blue-haired runt!
Spinning Cutter!
It's a shuriken!
Blue Cop! Burst Shot!
Way to go, Blue Cop!
One more shot!
Stealth mode, on!
Where did he go?
He's more like a ninja than a chameleon.
Haha! Yaah!
Oooh, look out! Don't take your eyes off me, now! Hah!
That kid over there, is that Jun?
I think it is!
And isn't that Theo over there too?
But what's that robot doing? Some kind of weird dance?
Quick, take a video!
Alright!
This is sure to get me some views!
Hahaha! Why don't you watch where you're going?
Blue Cop!
Megabolt...
Punch!
Aah!
I don't get it. How did you know where I was?!
You can only hide yourself by blending into your surroundings.
But it looks like you can't hide your shadow!
Don't think you've already won! Stealth mode, on!
Huh...? Uh-oh!
Blue Cop! Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt...
Smash!
What is this?!
What's with this wind??
Oh no, my phone!
Watch out!
Haha!
Blue Cop! Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Hey hey! Don't push yourself too hard.
I think we should switch out, Jun!
I won't give you the chance! Heli-Tornado!
Jun!
Blue Cop!
Don't worry!
How long do you think you can keep that up?
Blue Cop!
Haha!
Looks like I won, blue-haired kid!
Too bad! Looks like I won't become one of your underlings.
You keep saying underling...
but I have never made any Metal Cardbot my underling!
After acting so high and mighty, I don't need your excuses!
Well, what do you have to say? Is this kid your boss or what?
Jun, to us Metal Cardbots, is our...
Friend!
...A...friend?!
I don't get it! What are you talking about?
If you don't know, I'll tell you!
But only if you can defeat us!
What?
Let's have a rematch, Shadow X!
I promise I will seal you for sure!
Next time we meet, I'll be sure to blow you away with my Heli-Tornado!
That's what you think. But I have a secret weapon that can beat your Heli-Tornado!
Huh? A secret weapon?!
I-I accept your challenge!
Next time we meet, we will see if your secret weapon
can beat my Heli-Tornado!
I'm not leaving because I'm scared of some "secret weapon" or anything.
D-Don't take this the wrong way!
Jun!
Are you alright?
What is this secret weapon?
I would also like to know what it is.
Ah, about that...